hello everybody and welcome to Pam's
product reviews so I'm not gonna sell a
little lip plumping mask it's organic
these cool socks
their foot peeling socks what their you
can reuse these if you wash them and
then the companies that have high get
attacked Highlander cuz we love that
cheekbones this highlighter doesn't make
our cheek those are the Meryl Streep's
baby honey we got another problem
oh this is my mascara but I use it to
call the Lancome Hypnose drama this done
worse
amazing guys it's the best not only get
the little tips it's cheaper and the
lettuce for like two years so slick
perfect good night alright but this is a
better try them out first the first
thing I'm gonna be using is to put socks
oh well what's it supposed to smell like
mint sparkling cool it fresh like a
memento whoa it smells like nail polish
remover maybe that's how it's gonna
remove all word that's good there packet
[Applause]
can't even read them the didn't dog
try me oh there's been foot may fall off
wouldn't use it boom just keep one elbow
and if believe it's like supper one hour
would okay let's get that this is what a
stocking
oh my gosh you got drip all over the
places Rose my feet definitely do it and
oh okay now we're gonna let their feet
soaking let's use our next property oh
oh there's a sparkle Emily
he says to leave Iran freakin five
minutes before washing off you have oh
wait but it's only feeling soon
differently feel some tingling
sensations don't they look bigger amid
[Applause]
all right guys I think that's been
enough time to there look any bigger
dress
like they're hacci booms ladies let's
get the doin smells like beautifulness
okay I'm definitely seeing that shine
girl whoa this is the forks amazing
slender nose oh cool
well guys this has been the best profit
review than ever
so more the kind of be sure to subscribe
and comment to my channel which product
that you like the best and don't let you
guys know another flip sucks turnout I
have to keep well for an hour you are
beautiful